Hi, hi! It's me, Pip! Today, we're going to explore farm animals!
Look! A cow!
The cow says... MOO!
Moo! Moo! Can you say moo?
Sniff, sniff... let's see a REAL cow!
Yes! A real cow!
The cow says moo. Moo!
Did you hear the cow say moo?
Look! A sheep!
The sheep says... BAA!
Baa! Baa! Can you say baa?
Sniff, sniff... let's see a REAL sheep!
Yes! A real sheep!
The sheep says baa. Baa!
Did you hear the sheep say baa?
Ha! Its wool looks like a cloud!
Look! A chicken!
The chicken says... CLUCK!
Cluck! Cluck! Can you say cluck?
Sniff, sniff... let's see a REAL chicken!
Yes! A real chicken!
The chicken says cluck. Cluck!
Did you hear the chicken say cluck?
Look! A pig!
The pig says... OINK!
Oink! Oink! Can you say oink?
Sniff, sniff... let's see a REAL pig!
Yes! A real pig!
The pig says oink. Oink!
Did you hear the pig say oink?
We heard the cow say moo!
We heard the sheep say baa!
We heard the chicken say cluck!
We heard the pig say oink!
Moo, baa, cluck, oink!
Can you say them too?
Great exploring today! Wiggle your nose... bye bye, see you next time!